rankonesport.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Rank One Sport

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**LAST UPDATED: 0** **4/10/2017**

In an effort to make website Terms and Privacy information easier to understand for most visitors, AllPlayers Network is joining other software providers and adding a new section called WHAT YOU WANT TO KNOW, which provides a summary of critical information most visitors are seeking. 

**WHAT YOU WANT TO KNOW**

AllPlayers uses industry standard cookies to track very basic information about your actions on our Site, such as landing pages, exit pages, time on the site, location (as in city you are from, not home address), operating system and search terms used to locate us. That is not a complete list, because there are forms people fill out to participate in activities and other interactions you have with the school and/or military base using our software. However for most people who assume websites are tracking every little bit of data about them you may rest assured AllPlayers is not that type of site, nor do we have partners who would support malicious tracking. With that said it is always a good idea to keep your cookies and sessions cleaned out frequently, because Google, Amazon and virtually every large organization are very good at tracking your actions, and we do use them to help with some services. 

For example we use Google Adwords to place ads relevant to you on our site, and we use Google Adsense to track the information listed above. We also use Amazon AWS to manage and host some of our storage and services. Because we use Google Adsense, and they know a lot about your web activity you may see advertisements that are unrelated to our Site, but this does not mean our Site knows anything it is just Google. 

Third-party shared data. We have several brands we own, which are listed toward the end of the document, and because they have different URLs we call them third-party services. We share information between these services to make your utilization of our software easier, but we do not sell your information to third-party organizations. 

In summary, we do not sell your data, and we do everything we can to insure your trust and patronage is rewarded, not exploited. 

Now here is the legal stuff states, and merchant services providers require. 

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs the specific Internet website, application or other interactive service that includes an authorized link to this Privacy Policy and all other websites, applications and other interactive services you also use that are offered by AllPlayers Network, Inc., (“APN”) for use on mobile devices, tablets, personal computers and other devices, which includes the websites and online services, (collectively, the “Site”). By accessing any of the Site, you are consenting to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes what information the Site collects from users, including children, when they visit the Site; how such information is used and stored; when such information may be disclosed to third parties; how users, parents, and guardians can control the use and disclosure of collected information; and how information is protected.

Your privacy is important to us, and we recognize the need to provide additional privacy protection for children on the Site permitting such visitors. Our privacy practices are guided by the United States’ Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, as well as data privacy laws in the United States and other applicable countries. Younger visitors should always check with their parents or guardians before entering information on any website or mobile application and we encourage families to discuss their household guidelines regarding the online sharing of personal information.  
**  
**

**I.   INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE.**

We may request or collect certain information when you visit the Site. However, visitors are required to share only the information that is reasonably necessary to participate in the particular activity.  **_You may remove any information you provide to the Site at any time, at your sole discretion._**

A. Registration Information: The information required to register varies by Site, but may include: (a) birth date; (b) gender; (c) country; (d) state; (e) zip code; (f) user name and password; (g) wireless telephone number; (h) email address; and (i) other profile information such as identifiers, school, athletic information, communications preferences, and interests. If the Site either is directed to children under 13 or has actual knowledge that a user is under 13 years old, the child may be asked to provide his or her parent’s or guardian’s email address.

Registration information is used to enable visitors to log into their accounts across different devices and platforms; take advantage of the Site, Site’s service offerings; respond to requests for products, services, and information; send communications to users in connection with their account; manage schedules; serve appropriate material; customize the content you see when you visit the Site; and offer visitors special offers and promotions from the Site, as well as on behalf of selected third parties offering products, programs or services, that we believe may be of interest to you.

B. Social Platform Registrations and Social Media Plugins: Some of the Site permit or require users who are at least 13 years old to register or log into their account via a social networking platform such as Login with Facebook or Google, or permit you to use social media plugins such as the Facebook “Like” or Google “+1” buttons. When you use these social networking platforms and plugins, your username and password for the services and other information available about you or collected from you on these services may be shared with us.  
When you use social networking platforms and plugins, you share your information with them and their privacy policy applies to their collection, use, and disclosure of such information. In addition, they may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on the Site, and they may notify your connections on the social networking platform about your use of the Site. Such services may also employ unique identifiers which allow your activity to be monitored across multiple websites for purposes of delivering more targeted advertising to you.

C. Computer Information Collected by Us: When visitors come to a Site, we may automatically collect certain information from their computers or mobile devices, such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the visitor’s IP address, the web browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Safari, Chrome and Firefox), UDID (for certain mobile devices), information about the websites visited before and after visiting the Site, the web pages and advertisements viewed and links clicked on within the Site, interactions with e-mail messages sent by a site ( _e.g._ , links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded), information collected through the use of unique identifiers such as cookies (see below), information regarding the Internet service provider, and other standard server log information (“Computer Information”).

We may use cookies, web beacons, tokens or similar technologies (collectively referred to as “Tracking Technologies”) on the Site. “Cookies” (which may be html files, Flash files or other technology) are text files that help store user preferences and activity. “Web beacons” (also known as image tags, gif or web bugs) are small pieces of code used to collect advertising data, such as counting page views, promotion views or advertising responses. “Tokens” are unique persistent identifiers that are generated and sent from a server, such as Adobe’s Pass service, to a user’s device to identify an interaction session, such as the authentication for a user’s cable provider service, and which are usually stored as an HTTP cookie. The Site and/or third parties may use Tracking Technologies to collect Computer Information automatically as you browse the Site and the web.

We may use Tracking Technologies to help tailor our content, allow users to move between certain sites without logging into each site, enable the internal functioning of the Site, understand the Site and internet usage, improve or customize the content, offerings or advertisements on the Site, personalize your experience on the Site (for example, to recognize you by name when you return to the Site), understand your interactions with email messages originating from the Site (such as the links clicked on and whether the messages were opened or forwarded), save your password, save your settings, enable you to use shopping carts, help us offer you products, programs or services that may be of interest to you, deliver relevant advertising, maintain and administer the Site. These Tracking Technologies collect “click stream” data and additional other information regarding your visits to the Site (such as your visits to specific webpages, use of features, purchasing history or preferences), may collect such other information across multiple sessions on the Site and other websites and may also collect your IP address or some other identifier unique to the device you use to access the site (“Identifier”). An Identifier may be automatically assigned to any device you use to access the Site.  
By visiting a Site, whether as a registered user or otherwise, you acknowledge, understand and hereby agree that you are giving us your consent to set and access Cookies on your device and track your activities and your use of a Site through these Tracking Technologies and Identifiers and that we may use Tracking Technologies in the emails we send to you.

D. Computer Information Collected By Others: APN uses the services of third parties who may collect, use or disclose cookie information, IP addresses or other identifiers from devices and/or browsers of users who visit Site. Site use a variety of third-party advertising networks, data exchanges, traffic measurement service providers, marketing analytics service providers, and other third-party service providers (collectively, “Third Party Advertising Service Providers”) to, for example, serve advertisements on the Site, facilitate targeting of advertisements, and measure and analyze advertising effectiveness and/or traffic on the Site (“Targeting Services”). These Targeting Services enable us to display advertisements based on your visits to the Site and other websites you have visited and may include delivering advertisements or other content for products and services that may interest you. Targeting Services also help prevent you from seeing repeated advertisements and enable us to research the usefulness of certain advertisements.

These Third Party Advertising Service Providers do not have access to Tracking Technologies set by the Site except to the extent necessary to provide services to the Site. The Third Party Advertising Service Providers, as well as advertisers, may themselves set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your device if you choose to have Tracking Technologies enabled in your browser (or, for Flash cookies, if you have not removed them) and/or they may otherwise have access to other information about you. In addition, Third Party Advertising Service Providers may collect aggregate log data separately and independently from what the Site collect.

You should be aware that different rules might apply to the collection, use or disclosure of your information by third parties in connection with their advertisements, promotions and other websites you encounter on the Internet. The use of such technology by these third parties is within their control and not the Site. Even if we have a relationship with the third party, we do not control those sites or their policies and practices regarding your information and those sites may use the information they collect from you consistent with their own privacy policies, which we encourage you to review. We encourage you to research and direct any of your questions in this regard to these third parties.

E. Contests, Sweepstakes and Promotions: The Site may offer online contests, sweepstakes and promotions. To enter these contests, sweepstakes and promotions, you may be required to provide your first name and email address and/or additional information required for the management of the contest, sweepstakes or promotion.

F. Electronic Newsletters: Visitors can provide their email addresses to receive email newsletters and promotions from APN and our business partners. Visitors may change their preferences regarding emails at any time through the unsubscribe link in the newsletters or, for certain Site, by logging into and changing the preferences for their account.

G. Interactive Features and Services: Some of the Site offer interactive features and services, such as message boards and comment boxes. We use the information collected through interactive features and services to enable you to participate in such features and services.

H. Text Messaging Marketing and Promotions: Consistent with local law, appropriately aged visitors may have the opportunity to register for special promotions, services, news, programming and information delivered via text messaging (“Text Services”). If we do so, we will require your prior express consent for any Text Services in accordance with the nature of the Text Service and applicable laws, rules and regulations.  
When you register for Text Services, you acknowledge, understand and agree that you may be charged by your wireless carrier for the ability to send or receive all such messages. The standard messaging rates of your wireless carrier shall apply to all Text Services, unless noted otherwise. Under no circumstances will APN be responsible for any wireless email or text messaging charges incurred by such visitor or by a person that has access to a visitor’s wireless device, telephone number, or email address. If you change or deactivate your wireless telephone number, you agree to notify us when your wireless telephone number is no longer associated with you and identify such wireless phone number to ensure that future messages directed to you are not sent to the person to whom your old number has been or will be assigned. We may share your personal information with the operational service providers that assist us in delivering Text Services and similar services to you and as otherwise provided in Disclosure to Third Parties below.

I. Geolocation Information: We may collect and store information about your geographic location, but we will only collect precise geolocation information sufficient to identify street name and name of a city or town on Site that either are directed to users. You may be able to change the settings on your computer or mobile device to prevent it from providing us with such information. We use this information, for example, to enable visitors to take advantage of Site offerings; respond to visitor’s requests for products, services, and information; manage schedules; customize the content visitors see when visiting the Site; and to offer visitors special offers and promotions from Site, as well as on behalf of selected third parties offering products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to our visitors. By accepting this Privacy Policy and using the applicable Site, you hereby consent to the collection and storage of such geolocation information as described above.

J. Financial Information: We collect and use financial information, such as credit card numbers and security codes, as required for the use of the Site and its services.

K. Other Data Collection and Use.

We collect search query information when visitors search for information on the Site. We also collect information from visitors when they contact us with questions and comments.

We may use this information, along with any of the other information described above, to (i) analyze use of the Site and understand and improve our service offerings; (ii) prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; and (iii) for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your information or pursuant to your consent.

We may combine information collected through the Site with information we collect from other sources ( _e.g._ , social media integration services, offline records or publicly available information). It is your responsibility to provide complete and accurate information and to keep such information up to date. We are not responsible for any problem or liability arising from your failure to do so.  
**  
**

**II. DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES.**

We may share your information with third parties for the limited purposes described below. In the U.S., parents of children under the age of 13 have the option of consenting to the collection and use of their child’s personal information without consenting to the disclosure of that information to certain third parties.

A. Law Enforcement and Safety.

You acknowledge, consent, and agree to the extent legally permissible in your jurisdiction to allow us to access, preserve, and/or disclose the information we collect and/or content you provide to us (including information you may have posted on bulletin boards or internal site communication systems) to a law enforcement agency or other third parties if required to do so by law or with a good faith belief that such access, preservation, or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process; (b) enforce the Terms of Use of the respective Site; (c) respond to claims that the content violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; or (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the owners of the Site, any user of the Site, a third party or the general public. We also may disclose user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of others.

If you have concerns about the conduct of a particular user, please send an e-mail support@rankonesport.com.

B. Schools and Agents.

Information collected through the Site may be transferred, disclosed or shared with third parties, including but not limited to, schools and athletic departments, engaged by us to handle and deliver certain services and to perform other technical and processing functions. We may provide these third parties information collected as needed to perform their functions, but they are prohibited from using it for other purposes. Some of these agents, such as payment processors, may request additional information during the course of offering their services.

C. Third Parties/Advertisers.

APN uses the services of third parties who may collect, use or disclose cookie information, IP addresses or other identifiers from devices and/or browsers of users who visit Site. Some Site partner work with outside third parties to provide you with additional content, products, or services that they believe may be of interest. These partners operate websites and services that are separate and independent from the Site and, accordingly, may have their own privacy policies.

D. Co-Branded Sites and Features

Site offers co-branded services and features, such as events and promotions that we put together with other companies (“Co-Branded Partner”). Such services may be hosted on a Site and/or our Co-Branded Partner’s website. We may share your information with our Co-Branded Partner and your voluntary use of or participation in a co-branded service or feature means that you opt-in and affirmatively consent to both the Site and our Co-Branded Partner collecting and using the information you provided during registration and/or in connection with the specific co-branded feature for fulfillment, marketing or administrative purposes. If you wish to opt-out of a Co-Branded Partner’s future use of your information for marketing purposes, you will need to contact the Co-Branded Partner directly. 

E. Affiliated Businesses

The Site are part of a family of companies. Where permitted by law, we may share information we collect about you within the websites of our affiliated companies’ and other affiliated businesses so that we can, for example, provide you with information about products and services that might interest you.

F. Business Transfer

In the event that assets relating to one or more of the Site are transferred or sold to another entity as a result of, for example, a corporate sale, merger, consolidation, asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, information collected at the Site may be transferred to the acquiring company.

G. With Your Consent We may otherwise disclose your information pursuant to your consent.  
**  
**

**III.   SECURITY, STORAGE AND RETENTION OF INFORMATION.**

The Site maintain reasonable technical and organizational steps to help ensure that information collected is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers and use of electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access. The Site conduct financial transactions via secured transmissions. We limit access to visitor’s information to employees and contractors who are authorized for the proper handling of such information, and any employee found violating our standards of security and confidentiality will be subject to our disciplinary processes. We also take reasonable steps to help make sure our third-party agents protect the security of your personal information. However, as with most Internet sites or services, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully access such personal information through a number of means despite our efforts.  
Information collected at the Site will not be stored for longer than is necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, or to otherwise meet legal requirements.  
**  
**

**IV. ACCESSING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION.**

A. Reviewing Your Information

You have the right to access, update and correct factual inaccuracies in personally identifiable information that we collect online at the Site, subject to certain exceptions. To do so, you should log into your account or you may e-mail us at support@rankonesport.com.  To help protect your privacy and the security of your personally identifiable information, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access.  
See the Terms of Use for how registered users of this Site who are California residents and are under 18 years of age may request removal of content or information in postings.

B. Parental Access

Parents/guardians of children under the age of 13 can print out and mail or fax us a signed form that allows them to review any personally identifiable information collected about their child, have this information deleted, and/or request that there be no further collection or use of their child’s personally identifiable information. We will take steps to verify the identity of anyone requesting personally identifiable information about a child and to ensure that the person is in fact the child’s parent or legal guardian.

C. Deleting Information

You have the right to delete any information that you provide to the Site. To do so, you should log into your account and delete the information you wish to remove from the site.    
**  
**

**V. LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES.**

The websites that comprise the Site may contain links to other sites, including those of service partners, sponsors, advertisers, social networking platforms, and survey companies. These other websites are governed by their own privacy policies or information collection practices, which may be substantially different from ours. We encourage visitors to other websites to review the privacy policies and information collection practices of those websites.  
**  
**

**VI. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS.**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our visitors who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to or write us: support@rankonesport.com email, or you may contact us via regular mail at:

4145 BELT LINE ROAD  
#212-353  
ADDISON, TX 75001

This document is the sole statement of the Site’s Privacy Policy and no summary, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, including, without limitation, machine-generated, is valid.  
**  
**

**VII. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTICE.**

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason in our sole discretion by posting an updated Privacy Policy without advance notice to you. Such revisions shall be effective immediately upon posting and if you use the Site after they become effective it will signify your agreement to be bound by the changes. We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy often for updates.  
**  
**

**VIII. CONTACT US**

If you have any other questions about our information handling practices, including our practices with respect to children’s personal information, please contact us at:

4145 BELT LINE ROAD  
#212-353  
ADDISON, TX 75001  
888-544-3637
